{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "How many values and principles Agile has?",
      "answers": [
        "Two",
        "Three",
        "Four",
        "Five"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "2",
      "level": "1",
      "team": "Hawk"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is an Agile role?",
      "answers": [
        "Product owner",
        "Manager",
        "Secretary",
        "Lab Worker"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "0",
      "level": "2",
      "team": "Hawk"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is one of the\n formal reviews process?",
      "answers": [
        "improvise a session with group of members",
        "post review activities",
        "talking with the manager about sessions",
        "gathering results"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "1",
      "level": "1",
      "team": "Hawk"
    },
    {
      "question": " Is TDD an Agile methodology?",
      "answers": [
        "Yes",
        "No",
        "I dont know",
        "we didnt learn about it"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "0",
      "level": "1",
      "team": "Hawk"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is quality analyst in testing?",
      "answers": [
        "quality assurance throughout hardware development life cycle",
        "quality assurance and solving bugs ",
        "applies the principles and practices of software quality assurance",
        "testing hardware issues"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "2",
      "level": "1",
      "team": "Hawk"
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you use QA in Agile?",
      "answers": [
        "talk with the manager once in two weeks",
        "Attend daily stand ups",
        "send updates evrey two weeks",
        "in agile we work seperately"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "1",
      "level": "2",
      "team": "Hawk"
    },
    {
      "question": "When does the requirements step gets into the project ?",
      "answers": [
        "In the first levels",
        "level after design",
        "before writing the first document",
        "In the development stage"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "1",
      "level": "2",
      "team": "Hawk"
    },
	{
      "question": "which of type following is highest degree\n of integration in cloud computing?",
      "answers": [
        "Caas",
        "Aaas",
        "Paas",
        "Saas"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "3",
      "level": "2",
      "team": "Hawk"
    },
	{
      "question": "which of the architecture layer is used as\n front end in cloud computing?",
      "answers": [
        "client",
        "cloud",
        "soft",
        "all of the mentioned"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "0",
      "level": "2",
      "team": "Hawk"
    },
	{
      "question": "which of the architecture layer is used as\n front end in cloud computing?",
      "answers": [
        "client",
        "cloud",
        "soft",
        "all of the mentioned"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "0",
      "level": "2",
      "team": "Hawk"
    },
	{
      "question": "which of the architecture layer is used as\n front end in cloud computing?",
      "answers": [
        "client",
        "cloud",
        "soft",
        "all of the mentioned"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "0",
      "level": "3",
      "team": "Hawk"
    },
	{
      "question": "which of the architecture layer is used as\n front end in cloud computing?",
      "answers": [
        "client",
        "cloud",
        "soft",
        "all of the mentioned"
      ],
      "correct_ans": "0",
      "level": "2",
      "team": "Hawk"
    }
  ]
}
